错别字幕组
翻译 即将正式变身无业青年的电路 放假萌妹回来翻译
校对/特效 Sandy 压制 殷岂
克朗必须从追赶克朗的人手中逃脱
Kraang must evade those that pursue Kraang.
本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作的学习、交流之用。版权归原公司所有，禁止用于任何商业用途。请于下载后24小时内删除。
快点 凯西
Move it, Casey!
难道你以为大半夜的我在散步吗?
You think I'm on a midnight stroll?
抓紧啊!
Hang on!
他们带着钚走了
They're getting away with the Plutonium.
不能让他们跑了
Can't lose 'em.
啊 该死
Aw, crud.
你刚是拉了我的铁尺吗?
Are you pulling my sai?
走吧!
Let's go!
我好像又掉了一颗牙
I think I lost another tooth.
我了个...
What the....
谁会这么干呢?
Who could've done this?
事情变得更麻烦了
And it keeps getting worse.
他们拿走了钚
They took the Plutonium.
你觉得他们要它来干嘛呢?
What do you think they need it for?
不知道
No idea.
但是不管对方是谁 他们的火力都不容小觑
But whoever it was, packed some serious firepower.
只能希望他们是站在我们这边的了
Let's just hope they're on our side.
Teenage mutant ninja turtles
忍者神龟
teenage mutant ninja turtles
heroes in a half shell turtle power
半壳英雄 龟异能力
here we go, it's the lean green ninja team
冲吧冲吧 精英忍者
on the scene, cool teens doing ninja things
俊酷少年 忍术超群
so extreme out the sewer like laser beams
下水道上 激光喷发
get rocked with the shell shock pizza kings
真爱食物 只有披萨
can't stop these radical dudes
辐射变异 不能抵挡
the secret of the ooze made the chosen few
为守秘密 别无他法
emerge from the shadows to make their move
穿梭来回 阴影之间
the good guys win and the bad guys lose
正义必胜 邪恶必败
Leonardo's the leader in blue
李奥纳多 蓝带队长
does anything it takes to get his ninjas through
忍术精神 贯彻始终
Donatello is the fellow has a way with machines
紫带唐尼 精通机械
Raphael's got the most attitude on the team
红带拉夫 个性十足
Michelangelo, he's one of a kind
橙带麦奇 性格开朗
and you know just where to find him when it's party time
随时随地 欢乐无边
Master Splinter taught them every single skill they need
斯普林特 倾囊相授
to be one lean mean green incredible team
打造他们 成为精英
Teenage mutant ninja turtles
忍者神龟
teenage mutant ninja turtles
heroes in a half shell, turtle power
半壳英雄 龟异能力
忍者神龟
错别字幕组
就是那样 就是那样
That's where I want it. That's where I want it.
啊 耶 就要刷到高分了
Aw, yeah. About to hit the high score.
被抵消了!
- 耶 我们要成功了!   - 耶 帅呆了！
- Ah yeah， we're gonna do this! - Oh yeah, cool man!
此处双关 newtralize为S01E24时出现的蝾螈怪 neutralize是中和 抵消 中立的意思 中文双关无能 所以就这样了...
真是会消磨时间啊
Great use of your time.
而某些人则在外头暴揍克朗的脑袋
While somebody else is out there busting the Kraang's brains in.
而且不是我们
And that somebody wasn't us.
还有其他义务警员在追踪那些外星坨坨
We got other vigilantes out there going after those alien blobs.
我听着觉得不错
Sounds good to me.
可以少干点活了
Less work for us.
一点都不好
It's not good.
克朗偷走了钚
The Kraang stole Plutonium.
而把他们干翻的人 从他们那把钚抢走了
And whoever took 'em down stole it from them.
有意思
Interesting.
也许施莱德又跟克朗作起对来了
Maybe Shredder's going after the Kraang again.
我可不觉得那是施莱德的手下
I don't think these were Shredder's guys.
我知道幕后黑手的确切身份
I know exactly who's behind this.
你最好别又说是佩镭射枪的松鼠
You better not say squirrels with lasers again.
那么我们怎么办 李奥?
So what do we do, Leo?
要追踪那些追杀克朗的人吗?
Hunt down whoever's hunting the Kraang?
我想我们应该监视好这一带
I think we better blanket the area,
警惕一切
keep an eye out.
拉夫和凯西 继续监视胡同小巷
Raph and Casey, stick to the alleyways.
唐尼和麦奇 屋顶是你们的
Donnie and Mikey, you take the rooftops.
下水道我来负责
I'll cover the sewers.
半夜基地集合
We'll meet back at the lair at midnight.
你觉得你这次能跟上我吗 琼斯?
You think you can keep up this time, Jones?
你有什么不爽吗 拉夫?
What is your problem, Raph?
是因为消防通道的事吗?
The whole fire escape thing?
面对现实吧 凯西
Face it, Casey,
街头恶棍和机器忍者是一回事
street thugs and robo-ninjas are one thing.
但是从其他次元来的外星威胁那就是另外一个层次的了
But alien threats from other dimensions are a whole different ball game.
我单枪匹马地就把巨型太空虫子搞定了
I took on a giant space worm singlehandedly.
对啊 你是单枪匹马地被它吃掉了
Yeah, you were singlehandedly eaten by it.
你跟活肠子战斗过吗?
Have you ever fought living intestines?
我想没有吧
I don't think so.
底线问题 你在这件事上高估你自己了 凯西
Bottom line, you're in over your head on this one, Casey.
相信我
Trust me.
也许我没受过忍者训练 但是我的帅
I might not have ninja training, but I've achieved a level of awesome,
是只有凯西琼斯能达到的程度
attainable only by Casey Jones.
难以言喻
It's mystical.
哇啊 哥们 看这个 唐
Whoa, dude. Check it out, Don.
你看到这个被高温烤过的碳残留了吗
You see this carbon scorching?
他们是被某种等离子武器干掉的
They were taken out by plasma weapons of some sort,
这个技术跟克朗的技术一样先进
tech that's just as advanced as the Kraangs.
我们得提醒其他人
We got to warn the others.
克朗被那个不是克朗的人递给了克朗
The Kraang is getting their Kraangs handed to them, by those who are not Kraang.
不管这事是谁干的 把他们打击得相当彻底啊
Whoever did this not only destroyed them, they obliterated them.
噢 不好
Oh, no.
是克朗
It's the Kraang.
小菜一碟
Piece of cake.
等一下 头脑发热货 忍者都用潜入的
Hold on, hothead. Ninjas use stealth.
听说过吗
Ever heard of it?
刺头?
Spike?
那是你以前的宠物龟?
Is that your old pet turtle?
变异掉的那只?
The one who got mutated?
是的
Yeah.
他以前是叫刺头
His name was Spike.
现在叫刺霸了 还记得吗?
It's Slash now, remember?
很高兴又见到你 拉斐尔 想我吗?
Good to see you again, Raphael. Miss me?
刺霸 你在这干嘛
What are you doing here, Slash?
我们在解决克朗
We're taking care of the Kraang.
我现在有个新搭档了
I got a new partner now.
毁灭克朗!
Destruction to the Kraang!
太帅了
So awesome.
那是谁?
Who is that?
一个叫蝾螈怪的外星疯子
An alien psycho called the Newtralizer.
你们在干嘛 刺霸?
What are you guys doing, Slash?
做你们这些乌龟办不到的事情 消灭克朗
What you Turtles couldn't: Wiping out the Kraang.
别挡道
Keep out of the way!
好的 我来应付刺霸和蝾螈怪
All right, I'll take Slash and Newtralizer.
你退后点...
While you hang back and get...
啊 凯西
Aw, Casey.
贡噶啦!
Goongala!
小心!
Look out!
正是我想要的东西
Just what I was looking for.
然后是钚
And now the Plutonium.
刺霸 我们得到要找的东西了
Slash, we have what we came for.
看来你也有个新伙伴了啊 拉斐尔
See you got a new partner too, Raphael.
一个人类?
A human?
你也会像背叛我一样背叛他吗?
You gonna betray him the way you betrayed me?
还对过去耿耿于怀吗 刺头?
Still holding on to the past, huh, Spike?
我跟你说过了 我现在叫刺霸
I told you, it's Slash now!
我想我们有大麻烦了
I think we're in deep trouble.
我的头
My head.
拉夫 来点冰敷一下
Raph, ice me.
每集一卖萌的冰淇淋喵and什么都没有但什么都有的冰箱
你就不该参与这事 凯西
You should have never got involved, Casey.
刺霸和蝾螈怪太强大了
Slash and Newtralizer are way too powerful.
那两个呆比什么也不是 他们不过走狗屎运了
Those two goons are nothing. They lucked out.
没有下次了
Won't happen again.
大家专心点
Let's focus, people.
现在有两个疯了的变异生物到处乱跑
We got two crazy mutants running around.
破坏大街
Blowing up the streets.
我想我们应该盯紧克朗直到他们俩出现
I think we should shadow the Kraang until they show up.
这个简单
Easy.
既然刺霸和蝾螈怪是用钚来给他们的传送施加能量的
Since Slash and the Newtralizer are using Plutonium to power their teleportation,
我们可以追踪残留的辐射痕迹
we can look for traces of residual radiation.
麦奇 你能别把克朗的位置吃掉吗
Mikey, would you stop eating the Kraang locations?
等一下 唐 我就要刷新高分了
Hold on, D I'm about to get the high score.
就是...
And...
有入侵者
Intruders.
克朗必须提醒
Kraang must warn.
行动吧
Let's do this.
首先我们找到克朗的通讯设备
First we find Kraang communications.
然后把这个地方炸成拉卡拉卡洛卡拉卡
Then we blow this place to Raka Raka Roka Raka.
炸掉这个地方? 太危险了吧
Blow this place? Too dangerous.
街上的人类怎么办
What about the humans out on the street?
还记得我们相遇的那一天吗?
Remember the day we met?
那个誓言?
The vow?
我欠你一个人情 我叫刺霸
I owe you one. The name's Slash.
我听不懂你的话
I can't understand you.
我不得不救你
I had to help you.
他们是十个次元里最阴险的外星人
These are the most insidious aliens in the ten dimensions.
他们把我关进牢里 他们折磨我
They imprisoned me. They tortured me.
我发过誓 在我把他们全部消灭之前
I have made a vow never to rest,
我不会停下我的脚步
until I annihilate all of them.
我和你一起 兄弟
I'm with you, brother.
不惜一切代价消灭克朗
Destroy the Kraang at any cost.
"不惜一切代价" 对吗 兄弟?
"At any cost," right, brother?
你觉得是这里吗?
You think this is the place?
要么就在那里
Either that,
不然那里肯定在开碉堡的派对
or there's one bangin' party going on in there.
快 兄弟们 我们走吧
Come on, guys. Let's do this.
哇哦 哇哦 等等
Whoa, whoa, hold up.
谁让你来参加这次盯梢的?
Who invited you on this stakeout, anyway?
凯西 琼斯不请自来
Casey Jones invited himself.
是克朗通讯球
A Kraang communication orb.
这就是我要找的
Exactly what I was looking for.
能让我也知道计划如何吗?
Want to let me in on the plan?
会的
In due time.
是蝾螈怪
It's the Newtralizer.
我给他起了名的
I totally named that guy.
其实 是我起的
Actually, I named him.
"其实 是我起的"
"Actually, I named him."
快速地胖揍他一顿
Hit 'em hard and fast.
除了你 凯西 你退后
Except for you, Casey. You hold back.
又想挨揍了是吧 多纳泰罗?
Eager for another beatdown, Donatello?
离他远点!
Leave him alone!
凯西!
Casey!
你奶奶个大头鱼!
Holy mackerel!
快跑!
Run!
- 你们还好吧?   - 是的 没事
- You guys all right? - Yeah. We're cool.
没事? 没我你就被砸成肉酱了
Cool? You would've been flattened if it wasn't for me.
我也帮了你啊 拉夫
I've done the same for you, Raph.
哦 是吗? 啥时候的事?
Oh, yeah? When was that?
反正是各种时候
Like, dozens of times.
如果不是你拖慢进度 他们也不会跑了
If you didn't slow us down, they would've never gotten away.
你在搞笑么?
Are you kidding me?
为什么? 你觉得这是儿戏吗?
Why? You think this is a joke?
你猜怎么着 拉夫? 就这样吧
You know what, Raph? Forget this.
我走了
I'm out of here.
好极了
Good.
走就是了
Just go.
好 我走了!
Good. I'm going!
凯西 等等 等下
Casey, wait. Hold on.
怎么? 如果他耍孩子脾气 我就不需要他的帮助
What? If he's gonna act like a baby, I don't want his help.
这样不好 拉夫
Not cool, Raph.
人是有感情的 哥们
People have feelings, dude.
真正的 绵绵的 感情
Real squishy feelings.
呵 我又不是人
Well, I'm not people.
最好是有好事 唐尼
This better be good, Donnie.
我们在这上面干嘛呢?
What are we doing up here?
我们要监听刺霸和蝾螈怪的所有对话
We are gonna listen in on everything Slash and the Newtralizer say.
我在和刺霸摔跤的时候 我把间谍小强放在了他身上
While I was wrestling with Slash, I slipped a spyroach on him.
这个动作显然是脑补2333
我们可以从龟龟phone里面听到他们所有对话
We'll be able to hear everything they say through my T-phone.
我懂 酷毙了 对吧?
I know, awesome, right?
我真聪明
I'm smart.
挺好 我还以为你只是在被揍而已
Nice, and here I thought you were just getting beat up.
是啊 呃 这个 我多任务操作嘛
Yeah, well, uh, I was multitasking.
克朗通讯球发布了新的武器
The Kraang orb revealed a new weapon.
他们午夜要在码头实验
They're testing it on the docks at midnight.
我们可以用它一举铲除克朗
We can use it to wipe out the Kraang once and for all.
- 我们可以一起消灭整个肮脏的城市   - 还有里面每个无辜的人
- We can destroy this whole stinkin' city. - And every innocent human with it.
你是疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
我是来消灭克朗的 不是平民
I'm here to take out Kraang, not people.
我为什么要关心这个?
Why should I care?
我又不是人
I'm not people.
嗯 这句话有诡异的熟悉感啊
Hmm. Sounds oddly familiar.
如果时机到了
If it comes down to it,
我不会冒险的 兄弟
I won't take any chances, brother.
好吧 这下来真的了
Okay, this just got real.
我们要制止它
Let's end this.
这是他们说的新武器吗?
Is that the new weapon they were talking about?
哦 看上去不怎么样啊
Oh, doesn't look like much.
当我没说
Never mind.
克朗 在这
Kraang, over here.
朝被称为这边的方向前进
Move in the direction known as this way.
克朗锁定目标
Kraang targeting target.
这就是所谓的赞
That is what is known as awesome.
神奇的点赞姿势
拉卡 拉卡 洛卡 拉卡
Raka Raka Roka Raka.
计划是这样的
So here's the plan.
你分散克朗的注意
You distract the Kraang,
我去劫持步行器
I'll hijack the walker.
我是要信任你去操作那个机器吗?
And I'm supposed to trust you inside that thing?
我知道怎么控制 而你也别无选择
I know how to pilot it, and you don't have a choice.
计划是这样
Here's the plan.
刺霸 拖住克朗
Slash, keep the Kraang busy.
我去拿下步行器
I'm going for the walker.
克朗 攻击一切非克朗
Kraang, attack all non-Kraang.
重复 攻击
Repeat, attack.
克朗 小心克朗
Kraang, watch out for Kraang.
笨克朗
Stupid Kraang.
这啥都不是
Here goes nothing.
克朗步行器被克朗劫持 劫持者为外星两栖类
Kraang walker has been Kraang-jacked. By the alien amphibian.
克朗 撤退 撤退
Kraang, retreat, retreat.
刺头!
Spike!
你
You.
你救了我 拉夫
You saved me, Raphael.
我要把你们都消灭
I'll destroy you all.
拉卡 拉卡 洛卡 拉卡
Raka Raka Roka Raka.
你在干什么? 打克朗的时候他们帮了我们
What are you doing? They helped us fight the Kraang.
这是我的战斗 我不需要他们
This is my battle. I don't need them.
刺霸  你怎么能这样 兄弟?
Slash, how could you, brother?
你不是我的兄弟
You're no brother of mine.
拉夫!
Raph!
接到你了 哥们
Caught you, bro.
拉卡 拉卡 拉卡
Raka Raka Raka.
拉卡 拉卡 洛卡 拉卡
Raka Raka Roka Raka.
贡噶啦!
Goongala!
凯西? 你回来了?
Casey? You're back?
我寻思等你们全部遇到麻烦的时候
I figured I'd wait for you all to be in trouble,
我再闪亮登场救你们
and then I'd make an awesome heroic entrance.
帅吧 对不?
Pretty cool, right?
耶!
Yeah!
嗷 帅
Aw, yeah.
你被抵消啦 小样
You've been newtralized, son.
neutralize是抵消 中和的意思
哦 耶!
Aw, yeah!
谢谢 刺头
Thanks, Spike.
不...是刺霸
I mean... Slash.
你知道 我们队里总还需要一个人
You know, there's always room on the team for one more.
我要走自己的路 拉斐尔
I need to go my own way, Raphael.
我觉得我还是一个人好些
Think I'm better off solo.
再见 兄弟
Goodbye, brother.
将来会和大家再见的
I'll see you all again someday.
再见...刺头
Goodbye...Spike.
别焦虑 拉夫
Don't sweat it, Raph.
凯西 琼斯永远在你这边
You still got Casey Jones on your team.
干得漂亮 凯西
You did awesome, Casey.
是乌龟的最佳伴侣
Best partner a turtle could have.
今天事太多了 大伙
It's been a long day, guys.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
拉卡 拉卡 拉卡
Raka Raka Raka.